格塔纳纳 1347年
朝赞课时你人呢?为什么不在?
Where were you during Lauds? Why did you miss Lauds?
她昨晚跑了 我必须找到她
She got out last night, and I had to find her.
花了我一整个上午
Took me all morning.
她又出来了? - 是
She got out again? - Yeah.
她是穿过大门的?
Do you think she's getting through the gate?
你觉得她能穿过大门吗?
You think she could get through the gate?
我应该去检查大门
I should check the gates.
也许她是穿墙
Or maybe she got through the wall.
她怎么可能穿墙?
How would she get through the wall, though?
我不知道 驴子值得你那么关心?
I don't know. Why do you care about the donkey so much?
因为没道理啊
Just doesn't make any sense.
你为什么穿黑袍?现在是春天
Why are you wearing your black habit? It's spring.
因为我出去的时候 天已经黑了
Because it was dark when I left,
这件离我最近 我随手抓起的
and it was the closest thing to me, so I grabbed it.
我现在去换衣服
I'm gonna change.
这么多问题干嘛?
Why are you asking me so many questions?
早晨好 修女们
Beautiful morning, Sisters.
别他妈的跟我们说话 爬虫
Hey, don't fucking talk to us! - Fucking creep.
叫你不要跟我们说话 你这坨屎 - 你竟敢这样 混蛋
I told you to never talk to us, you piece of shit! - How dare you, fuckers!
滚开
Get the fuck out of here!
主啊 您有福的艺术 教我领会汝的意志
Blessed art thou, O Lord. Teach me to know thy will.
用这些唇 让汝的奖赏被记录下来
By these lips, let the awards thou makest ever be recorded.
欢欣 我等发现了这笔伟大的财产
Blithely, as one that has found great possessions,
我听从您的命令
I follow thy decrees.
使我思虑 我仍背负您判定的罪名
Bethinking me still of the charge thou givest,
我会记下汝之足迹
I will mark thy footsteps.
签下契约 作为我的喜悦
Be thy covenant ever my delight,
汝之言语 留在记忆中
thy words kept in memory.
主基督为我们受了诱惑和苦难
Christ the Lord was tempted and suffered for us.
来吧 让我们崇拜他
Come, let us adore him.
你今天早上为什么没参加朝赞课?
So, why weren't you at Lauds this morning?
因为驴子跑到树林里了 我得去抓她
Because the donkey escaped in the woods, and I had to catch her.
驴子又逃走了?
The donkey escaped again?
是 我想她穿过了大门
Yeah. I think she got through the gate.
她穿过了大门
She got through the gate.
但是我保证不会再发生了
All right. Well... - But I'll make sure it doesn't happen again.
好吧 我会告诉妥玛索神父
Okay, good. I'll tell Father Tommasso.
亚历山大修女怎么了?
What's going on with Sister Alessandra?
她太过了
She's been so out of it.
我不知道 她爸爸可能来了
I don't know. Her dad's probably visiting or something.
再次?
Again?
是 她有妄想症
Yeah. She's fucking delusional.
是 她太妄想了
Yeah. She's so delusional.
她很可悲
She's pathetic.
就因为爸爸捐钱给修道院
Just because your dad gives money to the convent,
并不意味着你能为所欲为
doesn't mean you're gonna get everything you want.
是
Yeah.
那天我撞见她
I walked in on her the other day,
她只是直直盯着窗外
and she was literally just staring out the window
10分钟不动
for, like, 10 minutes, not moving.
真的?
Really?
她可能在做男人的白日梦
She's probably, like, daydreaming about some guy
天降神屌 神奇地带走她
that's gonna magically come and take her away from here.
就像 "祝你好运"
It's like, "Good luck."
我知道
I know.
玛利亚院长刚才跟你说了什么?
So, what was Mother Marea saying to you earlier?
没什么 管好你自己的事
Nothing. Mind your own fucking business.
好
Okay.
但我会的
But I'll do that, yeah.
如果你愿意 我可以打扫
I can sweep it if you want me to.
由于某种原因 那里老是杂乱无章
For some reason, it keeps getting unorganized,
我真的不确定是谁干的
and I'm not really sure who's doing that.
好吧 也许你去打扫地窖
Okay, yes, maybe you could sweep the cellar,
因为那很脏
because that's very dusty, you know.
地窖和祭坛
That's the cellar and the altar.
我可以重排熏香
I can organize all the incense,
不知为何 总是一团糟
because, for some reason, it keeps getting all messed up,
我真的不确定是谁干的
and I'm not really sure who's doing that.
院长 还有件事你应该知道
But also, Mother, there's something else you should know.
说吧
Yes?
昨晚晚餐...
Last night at dinner...
我看到拉提扎修女 拿了两份
Mmm-hmm. - I saw Sister Latizia take two portions.
我不知道 也许你没清点
I don't know. Maybe you're not counting,
也许这无关紧要
so maybe it doesn't matter.
以防你需要知道 是拉提扎修女拿的
Just in case you are, it was Sister Latizia.
我不认为你应该关心...
I don't think you should be concerning yourself
别人吃了多少
with the amount somebody is eating.
不同时期 需要的食物不等量
We all require different amounts of food.
有些日子多吃点 有时少吃
I know that some days I need more food, some days less...
仔细观察我的饭量
So, watching me eat so carefully,
那会让我不舒服
that would make me uncomfortable.
所以你最好别为此烦恼
So I don't think you should be bothering yourself with that.
是 院长
Yes, Mother.
嗨 爸爸
Hi, Dad.
嗨 甜心
Hi, sweetheart.
你好吗 我的天使?
How are you, my angel?
我很好 你好吗?
I'm good. How are you?
我很好 你看上去很漂亮
I'm well. You look beautiful.
谢谢
Thank you.
我能做什么
What I can make out.
你看起来棒极了 他们喂饱你吗?
You look terrific. Are they feeding you?
他们应该喂饱你 因为我们捐钱了
They should be feeding you, for all the money we send them here.
但你看起来很美
But you look beautiful.
谢谢  妈妈怎么样?
Thank you. Thank you. How's Mom?
妈妈很好 大家都好
Mom is good. Mom is... Everybody's well.
好啊 麦钱特·里卡多 他怎么样?
Good. The merchant Ricardo, how's he?
麦钱特·里卡多 很高兴你问起他 他很好
Merchant Ricardo, uh, yes. Glad you brought it up. He's good.
他问起过我吗?
Has he asked about me?
肯定 肯定他有提起
Sure. You bet he has.
上次你和我说话的时候
You know, last time you and I spoke,
我希望保密全部嫁妆的情况
I was hoping that we'd have the whole dowry situation locked up,
我们现在还没够
and, um, we're not there just yet.
他们要求很多钱
They're asking for a lot of money,
我们捐钱给修道院
and, you know, with the money we're sending here,
还有你的修女们和她们的孩子 所以...
and then to your sisters and their children, it's a...
花掉很多钱 并没有那么多进账 所以
There's a lot of money going out and not that much coming in, so...
如果我们少捐给修道院
But maybe if we sent less money here to the convent,
就可以存钱
we could save it up,
我甚至可以和老爸老妈一起住
and I could even come and live with you and Mom and...
我不认为少捐钱是个好主意
I don't think sending less money here is a good idea,
因为 这会严重影响家庭
because, uh, that would reflect badly on the family.
我知道你渴望结婚 宝贝
But I know how eager you are to be married, my baby.
但也许 也许那不是你的使命
I know, but maybe it's... Maybe that's not your calling.
你的刺绣怎么样了?你还在做吗?
How's your embroidery going? You still doing that?
很好 因为你很擅长于此
Good, 'cause you're so good,
也许这是你的使命
and maybe that's your calling, you know.
有些人的使命 是婚姻和家庭 温暖的家
Some people, it's marriage and family and the warmth of a home,
也许你的使命 就是精细刺绣
and maybe for you it's... It's the detailed embroidery.
请扬起
You know, keep... Please.
扬起你的下巴
Keep your chin up.
给我 给我一点甜美的笑容
Give me... Give me a little sugar.
嘿 宝贝
Hey, hey, sweetie.
爸爸爱你
All right. Daddy loves you.
我爱你
I love you.
好吧 你保重
Okay. All right, you take care, and...
你不 不要失去希望
You don't... Don't... Don't you lose hope.
基督的身体
The body of Christ.
阿门
Amen.
基督的身体 阿门
The body of Christ. - Amen.
你没事吧?
Are you all right?
基督的身体
The body of Christ.
亚历山大修女 你父亲的来访怎么样
So, Sister Alessandra, how was your father's visit?
好
Good.
好?
Good?
是 很好
Yes, it was good.
有潜在的求婚者吗?
Any potential suitors?
这不是他拜访的目的
That's not even what his visit was about.
我们都没谈过
We didn't even talk about that.
那他为何来访?
Then what was his visit about?
上帝
Oh, my God!
我叫你别他妈的看我们 你这个混蛋
Hey, I told you not to fucking look at us, you creep.
对不起 我是
I'm sorry. I am...
你为什么要和我们目光接触?
Why are you making eye contact with us?
看地面 你这该死的色狼
Look at the ground, you fucking pervert!
对不起 - 这是什么鬼东西?
I'm sorry. - What is this shit?
这是萝卜
This is a turnip.
那不是萝卜 是屎
That's not a turnip! It's shit!
你想让我们吃屎?你是坨屎
You expect us to eat shit? You're a piece of shit!
你是坨屎 你真恶心 - 对不起
Yeah, you are a piece of shit. You're disgusting! - I'm sorry.
你真是个恶心的混蛋
Yeah, you are a disgusting piece of shit!
你觉得我们会吃这种食物吗?
Think we can just eat any of this food?
我们快饿死了 你什么都做不好
We're fucking starving! You can't do anything right!
看这面墙 看看你建造的东西
Look at this wall! Look at the stuff you build!
太可怕了 你这个笨蛋
It's horrible, you fucking imbecile!
你在这里都做些什么?
What do you even do here?
求你了 - 竟敢和我们说话?
Please, please. - Think you can talk to us?
你竟敢直视我们?
You think you can look at us?
你知道我父亲是谁吗?
You know who my father is?
他活该
Yes! He deserves this!
他付给你工资 却什么都做不好 你这小耗子
He pays you good money to do nothing, you little rat!
你这该死的小老鼠
You're a little fucking rat!
这是什么蛆食物?
What is this, maggot food?
我们恨你 - 求你了
We hate you! - Please, please.
把所有的食物都囤积起来 像个犹太人?
Just hoarding all the food, huh, like a fucking Jew?
这就是你干的好事?
Is that what you're doing?
我们都快饿死了
We're all starving!
你知道你做了什么
You know what you did!
我们恨你
We hate you!
你该去死
You deserve to die!
都准备好了?
All right. Almost ready?
妥玛索 是的
Tommasso, yes.
都准备好了 - 看看这个
Almost ready. - Oh, look at this!
是不是很美?
Isn't it beautiful?
太棒了 谁干的?
That's gorgeous. Who did that?
亚历山大修女
Sister Alessandra.
我们得多做点
We have to make more of that.
城里很畅销的
That'll go big in town.
告诉卢尔克 关好花园的门
Tell Lurco to keep that garden gate closed,
因为鹿会进来的
because the deer are getting into it.
好吧
All right.
我的朋友
All right, my friend.
准备好出发了吗?准备好了吗?
Are you ready for a journey? Are you ready?
当树叶凋零
"Know when the leaf parts from the ash
树梢枯萎
"and the branches wizen in the treetop
树皮不再供给甜美的树液
"for through the bark, the sweet humor of the sap doesn't mount to them
鸟儿噤若寒蝉
"and the birds have fallen silent from their warbling
因为寒冷 攫取着他们
"because of the cold that grips them.
但是 我仍坚定不移
"But in spite of this all, I'm unshaken
因为我繁荣兴盛
"for I am rejuvenated and prosper
所有其他的幸福是白费
"when all the other happiness is wasted.
因为我所有的欢乐
"And if all my merriment is saddened
无需公开坦诚...
"to the point of not boasting openly..."
然而 它并没有阻止
"It hasn't however kept my praise
我的赞美...
"from gaining me..."
她们不是好人 - 不 卢尔克
They're not good people. - No, Lurco...
不 我要走了 修女们朝我吐口水
No, I'm leaving. The nuns, no. They spit on me.
谁朝你吐口水? - 她们向我吐口水
Who spit on you? - They spit on me.
卢尔克 我得走了
Lurco, I have to leave.
我正要去市场卖织物 拜托
I'm about to leave to go to the market to sell the fabrics, please!
神父 我很抱歉 她们朝我吐口水
Father, I'm very sorry, I'm very sorry. They spit on me.
她们叫我犹太人
They called me a Jew.
她们叫我犹太人 妥玛索神父 - 卢尔克 拜托你
They called me a Jew, Father Tommasso. - Lurco, please.
她们叫我犹太人- 拜托
They called me a Jew. - Please.
求你了 就再多等两天吧
Please, just wait two days!
我觉得我们过的不错
I want to think we've had a nice life.
让你尽享
I think I surround you in a lifestyle
愉快和奢华的生活
that is pleasant and luxurious.
享用这野鸡吧
Enjoy this pheasant.
佛罗伦萨一旦被占据
Soon as Florence gets here,
我们只能吃鸡了 和该死的克罗地亚人一样
we'll be eating chicken like a bunch of fucking Croatians.
我派了另一个信使去佛罗伦萨
I sent another messenger to Florence.
信使回来了
Messenger came back.
他碰到教皇派士兵
He's dealing with the Guelph soldiers.
他占了佛罗伦萨 他占了阿雷佐
He's got Florence. He's got Arezzo.
他还没有占领比萨 但他会的
He doesn't have Pisa yet, but he will,
然后他就会来找我们
and then he's coming for us.
所以我派了信使去阿雷佐
So, I sent a messenger to Arezzo.
他不在阿雷佐
He's not in Arezzo.
他在比萨
He's in Pisa.
他要...他在百般勾引比萨
He's going... He's making a play for Pisa!
比萨还没到手 但他会的
He doesn't have Pisa yet, but he will.
他们很虚弱 像教皇派
They're weak, like the Guelphs.
你知道比萨之后是什么吗?卢卡
You know what comes after Pisa? Lucca.
目的是为了丝绸贸易
He's coming for our silk trade.
亲爱的
So, my dear,
享受这奢华 你的两件套
enjoy this lavish lifestyle, your two dresses,
你的野鸡 你的小扁豆 好好享用吧
your pheasant, your lentils. Live it up.
快结束了
It's coming to an end.
佛罗伦萨的阴谋论
This... This Florentine conspiracy thing
言而总之
is getting to the point of, like,
他说了这么多 跟神经病一样
he talks about it so much, it's like a mental illness.
我会假装睡着
I'll be fake sleeping... - Mmm-hmm.
他还在继续说
And he's still going on about it.
"我们会失去一切"
"We're gonna lose everything." - Mmm-hmm.
我倒是挺喜欢的
And that's what... I'm like... At this point, I'm like,
"我反倒希望如此 好让你闭嘴"
"You know what? I hope we do, just so you'll shut up."
闭嘴
Just shut up. - Mmm-hmm.
他认为一切都是他们造成的
He thinks that everything that happens is because of them.
他废话连篇
Yeah, he says a lot of things.
他只是... 他的音调有多难听
He's just... Just, it's not... Even his tone is awful.
是吗?你以为我不受煎熬吗
Yeah? You act like I don't suffer through it, too.
我就在你旁边站着
I'm right there with you.
听起来像他
That sounded like him.
Hmm? - That sounded like him.
那不是他
No, no, that's not him.
他一直在睡觉 放松
He's always asleep. Just relax.
你真可爱
You're so cute.
我好像听到了... - 不
I felt like... I felt I heard the... - No, no.
那好 我们再做一次爱 帮你放松
All right, we're gonna fuck again. That'll help you relax.
不 就是他
No! That is him.
不 那是他
No! That's... That is him.
该死 该死
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
你做了什么?
What have you done?
我做了什么?
Oh, what have I done?
外面有什么?教皇派吗?
Oh, what's out there? Is it the Guelphs?
是佛罗伦萨吗?他们会来吗?去抓他们
Is it Florence? Are they coming? Go get 'em!
我等下找你算账
I shall deal with you shortly.
我吓呆了
I'm petrified.
明早我就知道你是谁了
Now I'll know who you are in the morning.
咱私下解决
We'll settle this in private.
我告诉你们 100%
I'll tell you what happened, 100%.
我们睡觉的时候 恶魔进来切了我们的头发
A demon came in here while we were sleeping and cut our hair.
无法证明它不是恶魔 所以
There's no way to prove it's not a demon, so...
它就是恶魔
Which means that it was a demon.
不然是什么?术士吗?
What else was it? A warlock?
早上好
Good morning.
君主大人
My liege.
你们这些低下的狗
You common-born dogs.
有个蠢蛋自认为他是个宫廷小丑
One of you sluts thinks he's quite the jester.
你他妈的在看什么?
What the fuck are you looking at?
我会操你呼吸的地方
I'll fuck you where you breathe.
那是怎么回事啊?
What was that all about, huh?
我看见那些教皇派冲进城里
I saw Guelph men rush into town...
野蛮的野兽 撕裂人体四肢
Savage beasts, tearing men from limb to limb.
我看到一个男人一靴子
I saw a little boy's head crushed between a...
踩爆了一个小男孩的头颅
A man's boot and... And a stone.
他的眼球掉了出来
His eyeballs came skittering across.
我看到了我漂亮的八岁妹妹 贝尼西亚
I saw my beautiful eight-year-old sister, Benicia,
被教皇派一剑劈成两半
cleaved in half with one swipe of a sword by the Guelphs.
她活到现在 会比你更漂亮
She was more beautifully developed as a woman than you are today.
你看到我铜色的头发吗?
You see this copper in my hair?
她全身的毛发 都是这种最美丽的颜色
She had the most beautiful hair of this color all over her body.
闭嘴
Shut up.
别在餐桌上说了
Stop talking about this, not at the table, okay?
别再碎碎念眼球 压碎一类的屁话
No more eyeballs or squishing and all that kind of stuff.
我不想在餐桌上 再听到任何暴力事件
I don't want to hear about any more violence at the table,
因为我在用餐 我在消化 所以拜托
'cause I'm eating, and I'm digesting, so stop it.
闭嘴
Silence!
你怎么敢?
How dare you?
你很软弱
You are weak.
我怀疑 你的血管里流淌教皇派的血液
I've begun to suspect you have Guelph blood coursing through your veins.
你又怎么知道?
Oh, no. How did you find out?
今晚我会到你的卧房 带着魔鬼刺棒
I will bring the Devil's goad to your bedchamber this evening,
闪闪亮亮
and it will be freshly polished.
不
No.
我们再也不做了
We're not doing that anymore.
你放不进去
You're not putting anything in there.
也拿不出来
Nothing's coming out, nothing.
我们等着瞧
We'll see about that.
我不会再这样了
I'm not doing that anymore.
我要再来一发 - 不
I need a refill. - Don't.
请不要这样做
Oh. - Please don't do this.
我只需要一小发
I just need a quick little refill. Come here.
过来 - 你疯了
Come here. - You're insane.
你太厉害了 - 停下 有人会抓住我们的
You've been so sweet to me. - Stop, stop. Somebody's gonna catch us!
听着 你会把我害死的
Look, look, you're gonna get me fuckin' killed! - Uh-huh.
如果有人抓住我
If someone catches me...
我不想弄疼你
I don't want to hurt you! I don't want to hurt you!
那就脱掉你的裤子 脱
Take your pants off, then. - No, get off!
怎么这么多机关?
It's like, why are there so many folds in here?
妈的 该死
Shit. Oh, shit.
把他的蛋给我取下来
Bring me his goddamn balls.
妈的 该死
Shit. Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
天啊 你的树枝到处都是
God dang it! Your twigs are all over the place.
跟上没有
Keeping up? You keeping up?
你先去 - 不带你吗?
Just go without me! - Go without you?
我会到的
I'll get there.
马赛托 让我们先谈谈
Masseto, let's talk about this!
快停下
Just stop! Stop!
马赛托 快
Masseto, come on!
马赛托 拜托
别跑了
No running!
马赛托
Masseto!
不
Oh, no!
No.
神父?
Father?
你离我远点 这些都是我的
You stay away! These are mine!
好像你...
No, it just looks like you...
你离我远点 东西是我的
You stay away! They're mine!
停下
Hey, stop! Stop!
我只是想帮你
I'm just trying to help you!
如果你是强盗 我就打你
If you're a bandit, I will strike you!
要么你丢了所有东西
You can either lose all of your stuff,
或者你可以相信我 让我帮你
or you can trust me and let me help you!
我被委托关照这些织物
I was entrusted to take care of these things,
我毁了这一切
and I've ruined this!
修女们做了一切
The sisters made all these things,
它们掉到水里了 - 没事的
and I've lost them in the water. - It's all right.
我倒了 - 没事 我会帮你的
And now I've fallen... - It's all right. I'm gonna help.
你没事吧?
Are you all right?
我醉了
I'm drunk!
我和车一起倒了
And I have fallen with my cart,
这只动物走错了方向
and this animal went the wrong way.
好了 别动
All right, all right, all right, all right, just stay down.
别起来
Stay down, please.
都在这里了
There. That's it. All right.
我希望能给你一些回报
I wish there was something I could give you in repayment.
我没有钱 或者酒 - 不 神父 我不需要钱或酒
I have no money. Or wine... - No, Father, I don't need any money, or wine.
没关系的
That's... That's totally fine. Yeah.
你确定不要报答吗?
Are you sure there's nothing I can do to repay you?
我不知道 如果你今晚有地方让我住
I don't know. If you maybe had a place for me to stay tonight,
我会很感激的
I would really appreciate it.
你无处可住?
You have nowhere to stay?
是的
No.
那你要跟我走
Oh, you're coming with me.
完全的灾难啊
It was a total disaster.
我不应该耗费时间和卢尔克理论
I never should have stopped to speak to Lurco.
结果我晚了
That's what's held me up.
到晚上才出发
And then I was out at night.
我喝了酒 因为我没有带水
I had to drink the wine, because I had no water.
喝着喝着我就醉了
And then I just didn't realize how drunk I was getting,
我丢了一切
and I've lost everything!
对不起 神父
I'm sorry, Father.
我希望我能做的更好
I wish there was more I could have done.
我要怎么解释啊?
How am I gonna explain?
不 没事的
No, no, it's all right.
你做了 你做了很多
You've done... You've done a lot.
给你新鲜的面包
Right, here you are. Fresh bread for you.
小心 慢点
Oh, careful. Go... Take it easy.
真的很好吃
It's really, really good.
对不起 我之前是如此...
Good, good. I'm... I'm sorry I was so...
兴奋和不安
Excited and upset before. I...
没关系
That's all right. That's...
你想喝点酒吗?
Would you like some wine?
喝个底朝天
Bottom up. Up.
干了
Up! Uh-uh...
我没用手
I didn't touch it.
这真是太棒了
This has been wonderful.
太棒了
Too wonderful.
多好的祝福啊
What a blessing!
我受到的最好祝福 - 你救了我
The best blessing I have ever experienced. - You saved me!
是你救了我 开什么玩笑?
You saved me! Are you kidding?
我没开玩笑
I'm not kidding.
我没救你
I didn't save you.
我一个人 不能把驴车的轮子装回去
I couldn't put it... The wheel of the donkey cart back on.
上帝保佑我 神父 因为我有罪
Bless me, Father, for I have sinned.
已经好几年了
It has been years,
距离我上次忏悔已经有很多年了
many years since my last confession.
我的罪过是
Hmm. - Here are my sins.
我睡了人妻
I have slept with another man's wife.
他是贵族 他是我的主人
He's a nobleman, and he is my master.
那是通奸
Well, that's adultery.
我知道
I know.
这是很严重的罪过
It's a very serious sin.
有时
Sometimes...
她会把嘴巴放在我的性器上
She would place her mouth around my sex.
那是鸡奸
Well, that's sodomy.
又一个严重的罪过
It's also a serious sin.
那也是鸡奸了 如果
Is it also considered sodomy if...
如果我把嘴放在她的性器上
If I placed my mouth on her sex while...
我们俩同时进行的
She simultaneously had... Had her mouth around mine?
你为什么要这么做?
Why would you do that?
因为她喜欢
Because she... She liked it.
喔
Oh.
对 那也是鸡奸
Well, yes, that's also sodomy.
我以为鸡奸是
I thought sodomy was... Was just when I would...
穿过后庭花
When someone would penetrate the rear... The rear end.
没错 那也是鸡奸
Yes, that's... That's also sodomy.
传统的鸡奸 - 好吧
That's the traditional form of sodomy. - Right.
你干了?
Did you do that?
是我干的 确实发生了
I... I did. Yes, I... That also occurred.
但你没有把种子洒在后庭花?
But you didn't spill your seed in the rear end?
不 我没有
No, no, I did not.
很好 很好
Good, good.
我会把种子洒在她身上
I would spill my seed on her... Um...
比如背部或双峰
On her back or on her bosom.
但大多数时候 她会要求
But most of the time, she would request
颜射
that I spill my seed all over her face.
好吧
Well...
这些都是严重的罪过
These are serious sins.
你后悔吗?
And do you regret doing these things?
我已经吸取了教训 真的
I've learned my lesson, I really have.
我只是 我不想再当那个人了
And I just... I don't want to be that person anymore.
如果我回去 他们会抓住我
If I go back out on the road, they will catch me,
他们会杀了我
and they will kill me.
好吧 我给你忏悔
Well, I'll give you your penance.
你念10遍万福玛利亚 - 是
I want you to say. - Yeah.
还有15遍天父
And 15 Our Fathers.
是
Yes.
现在 至于其他情况
Now, as to the other situation
你被追捕的事
about you being pursued,
我想我可能有解决方案
I think I may have a solution
这对我们两个人都是个祝福
that can be a blessing to both of us.
谢谢你 神父 谢谢
Yes, thank you, Father. Thank you.
早上好 玛利亚 - 早上好
Good morning, Marea. - Good morning.
现在有空吗? - 是
Is it a good time? - Yes.
我给你介绍一下 这是马赛托
I'd like to introduce you to someone. This is Masseto.
他是个聋哑人
He's a deaf-mute. - Oh.
我外出时遇到他 和他的家人交谈过
I met him on my trip and spoke to his family,
他们向我解释说 他非常擅长园艺 轻木工
and they explained to me that he's very good with gardening, light carpentry.
我想他可以帮我们修葺修道院
I think he could help us repair the cloister
接手所有卢尔克的活儿
and do all of the things that Lurco was doing.
既然他是个聋哑人
And I thought the fact that he's a deaf-mute,
与修女们的冲突将会少很多
there would be a lot less conflicts with the sisters.
真不敢相信你外出遇到了聋哑人
I can't believe you met a deaf-mute on your trip.
外出怎么样?织物卖掉了吗?
How was your trip? Did you sell any fabrics?
我们应该私下谈谈
We should talk about it in private.
反正他是聋哑人嘛
But you said he was a deaf-mute.
对
Right. Um...
我被抢了
I was robbed.
你受伤了吗?没有
Were you hurt?
我很好
No, no, no. I'm fine.
我没有受伤 但强盗夺走了一切
I wasn't hurt, but the bandits took everything.
他们抢走了所有的刺绣和丝绸
They took all the embroidery, all of the silk,
所以我没有卖掉
so I made no sale.
我空手回来了 对不起
I've come back empty-handed. I'm sorry.
我能说什么呢?虽然我很尴尬
What can I say? I'm very embarrassed, but...
但是算了
It's gonna be fine.
不要担心太多 我会让他开始工作的
All right. Don't worry too much about it. I'll get him started.
我们走
We go. We go.
你好
Hi.
你是谁?
Who are you?
我是吉尼芙拉修女
I'm Sister Ginevra.
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
你在挖沟?
You're digging a ditch?
你在挖沟
You're digging a ditch.
好吧
All right.
因为上帝是完美的
Since God is perfect,
我们的工作是 与他"精神的实在"和谐相处
it's our job to live in unison with His essence.
但有时很难找到幸福
But sometimes it's difficult to find that happiness
事情不像我们想的那样
and things don't go our way.
我们觉得我们被惩罚了 而不是...
And we feel like we're being punished, and it's not...
谢谢你 费尔南达修女 谢谢
Thank you, Sister Fernanda. Thank you.
当然
Of course.
但是上帝 上帝是完美的
But God... God is... Is perfect.
费尔南达 够了
Fernanda! That's enough!
什么?  - 这是
What? - This is...
维欧拉 进去读完你的书
Viola, go inside and finish your reading.
停下
Stop it! Stop that!
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
我说了住手 够了
I said stop that! That is enough!
你今天怎么了?
What's gotten into you today?
没什么 我很抱歉
Nothing. I'm so sorry.
我去清理粪便或擦洗地窖
You know what? I'll just go scoop some dung or scrub the cellars...
我不知道这算什么意思
I don't know where this is coming from!
免得你进来的时候 打扰到你
And not bother you while you walk in...
他刚才对你笑了吗?
Did he just smile at you?
我不知道
I don't know.
他为什么笑?那是谁?等等
Why is he smiling? Who is that? Wait!
你他妈的是谁?
Who the fuck are you?
你是谁?
Who are you?
费尔南达 住手
Fernanda, stop!
他是个不速之客 我不知道他到底是谁
He's an intruder. I don't know who the fuck he is!
我去喊玛利亚院长
Let me get Mother Marea!
好 去吧
Fine! Go!
说你是谁
Tell me who you are.
什么 说点什么
What? Say something!
你从哪里来?搞什么鬼?
Where did you come from? What is that?
你这鸡爪疯干什么的?
What are you doing with your hands?
干嘛 你饿了吗?
What? What, are you hungry?
那是什么 鸟吗?你在祈祷?
What is that, a bird? You're praying?
你他妈的在跟我说什么?
What the fuck are you saying to me?
他妈的告诉我你是谁
Fucking tell me who you are!
别砍他的头
Don't chop his head off!
他是马赛托 他是聋哑人 为我们工作
He's Masseto! He's a deaf-mute! He works for us!
妥玛索神父雇了他
Father Tommasso hired him.
很抱歉 我没告诉你
I'm sorry I didn't tell you about it.
你总是抱怨卢尔克和你说话
You're always complaining about how Lurco talks to you,
马赛托不说话
and Masseto doesn't talk.
所以 我真的希望你给他一个机会
So, I would really like you to give him a chance.
拜托
Please!
好吧
All right.
修女 我要和你谈谈
And, Sister, I need to speak to you.
你现在可以起来了
You can get up now!
他听不见
He can't hear you.
你为什么要为他辩护?
Why are you defending him?
现在
Now!
妥玛索神父被一群强盗袭击
Father Tommasso was attacked by a group of bandits, and...
不 - 他...
No. - He...
所有的刺绣都被偷了
Well, all the embroidery was stolen.
所以我所做的一切 都消失了吗?
So everything I've done, everything I've worked on, is gone?
恐怕就是这样了
Yes, I'm afraid that's what happened.
你没事吧?
Are you all right?
没事
Yeah.
只是...
It's...
我知道这很难...
I know this is a lot to...
吞下这口气
To swallow.
我会很高兴 派人
I'd be more than happy to get you
与你一起干 需要加倍努力
extra help for the work, which will be doubled
才能弥补失去的一切
to make up for everything that was lost.
你好?
Hello?
你好
Hi.
我弄坏了这个
Um, I broke this.
你能
Can you...
修好它吗?
Fix this, yes?
你的眼睛真和蔼
You've... Really kind eyes.
抱歉把这个给你
Sorry to just spring this on you.
因为刺绣都是我的事
It's only 'cause they just sprang it on me.
她们就知道让我加倍生产
You know, they just asked me to double production
莫名奇妙的刺绣
of my embroidery out of nowhere.
我基本上是单干
And I'm basically doing it alone.
她们说 给我协助
They told me that they would give me help,
然后 派给我的是
and then they just stuck me with this...
一个干瘪的老女人
This, like, shriveled up, old, comatose woman.
而且 我看着她 我觉得
And, you know, I look at her, and I just...
看到了我自己
I see me.
那就是我的未来
That's what I'm gonna become.
我会废在这里
I'm just gonna waste away here.
这可不是我的梦想
This is not what I imagined for myself, you know.
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
你为什么像动物一样躲在杂草里?
Why are you hiding in the weeds like an animal?
我刚看到亚历山大修女走进工具间
I just saw Sister Alessandra go into the toolshed.
但我知道 他没有攒钱给里卡多
But I know he is not saving up money for merchant Ricardo.
这根本不是他的错
This is like... It's not even his fault.
世界上任何地方都没有希望
There's just no hope anywhere in the world.
如此的悲伤和压抑
It's so sad and depressing.
我们任何人都没有希望
There's no hope for any of us.
是啊 看看你
Yes, look at you.
看看你 你不能说话 你听不到 这不公平
Look at you. You can't speak. You can't hear. It's not fair!
你只是被这些烂事缠住了
You're just stuck here with all these bitches,
我也是
and so am I!
我都不知道该怎么办
I just don't even know what to do!
太不公平了
It's so unfair.
她他妈的在里面干什么?
What the fuck is she doing in there?
我不知道
I have no idea.
让我们祈祷
Let us pray.
主啊 让我们的身体安息吧
Lord, give our bodies restful sleep
让我们今天所做的工作
and let our work we have done today
是为永恒的收获而播种
be sown for an eternal harvest
通过基督 我们的主
through Christ, our Lord.
阿门
Amen.
主啊 给我们安静的夜晚 完美的结束 阿门
Lord, grant us a quiet night and a perfect end. Amen.
上帝保佑我 神父 因为我有罪
Bless me, Father, for I have sinned.
距离我上次忏悔已经三天了
It has been three days since my last confession.
你想忏悔什么?
And what is it you would like to confess?
昨天 我走过花园
Yesterday, I walked by the garden,
我挑了个萝卜 全吃了
and I picked a turnip and I ate the whole thing,
我没有和修女们分享
and I didn't share it with my sisters.
你后悔吗?
Hmm, and you regret this?
是的 神父
Yes, Father.
因为贪婪 不是吗?
Because it was greedy, wasn't it?
是 神父
It was, Father. - Hmm.
还有别的吗?
Anything else?
有 神父
Yes, Father.
我的动机不纯
I've been having impure thoughts.
你有没有对这些动机采取行动?
And have you acted on these thoughts?
没有 神父
No, Father.
上帝保佑我 神父 因为我有罪
Bless me, Father, for I have sinned.
距离我上次忏悔已经两天了
It's been two days since my last confession.
你想忏悔什么?
And what do you wish to confess?
有一天 我在花园里发现了一个萝卜
The other day, I found a turnip in the garden
我一个人吃掉了
and I ate it all by myself,
我没有和修女们分享
and I didn't share it with my sisters.
它是如此美味 - 修女
And it was so delicious... - Sister.
吉尼芙拉刚跟我说了同样的故事
Ginevra just told me the same story.
你听过她的忏悔?
Did you overhear her confession?
没有
No.
好
Fine.
你还有什么要忏悔的吗?
Do you have anything else to confess?
我没有别的要忏悔的了
No. I have nothing else to confess.
你错过了朝赞课 修女
Well, you missed Lauds, Sister. That's something.
那是因为驴子跑到树林里 我救了她
Well, that's because the donkey escaped in the woods, and I saved her.
你应该感谢我 神父
You should be thanking me, Father.
听着 我正要
Look, I'm just gonna...
我不知道该怎么做
I don't know what to do here.
如果你不忏悔 上帝不能原谅你
If you don't confess, God can't forgive you, so...
我没什么可忏悔的
I have nothing to confess.
好吧 那就去考虑一下你做了什么
All right. Well, just go and think about what you've done.
我们下周再试一次 - 是 神父
Let's try it again next week. - Yes, Father.
第一天
First day.
第一天 谢谢
First day. Thank you.
你活下来了
You survived.
过得怎么样?
How's it going?
没什么 所有的工作都很顺利
Yeah, no... All the work itself, it went really smoothly.
我在修道院做了很多工作
And I did a lot of great work in the cloister,
那很好
and that was good.
我遇到了一些修女 她们
And I met a few of the... The sisters, and they were...
她们是 非常有趣
They were... They were, you know, very interesting.
只是感激 感激来到这里 所以
And just grateful... Grateful to be here, so...
这些女孩可不好对付 我不打算撒谎
These girls can be tough. I'm not gonna lie.
她们可能非常强硬 - 真的?
They can be very tough. - Really?
还有暴力
And violent.
暴力?我...
Violence? I...
我觉得很难相信
Wow, I just... I find that so hard to believe.
她们太可爱了
They were... They were so lovely.
她们会攻击人身
They physically have attacked people.
如果发生什么事 就告诉我
So, if anything happens, just tell me.
我
Yeah. I...
不管什么 我都能修好 但你得告诉我
Whatever it is, I can fix it, but you have to tell me.
我的意思是 聋哑是为了保护你
I mean, this deaf-mute thing is there to protect you...
对
Exactly.
远离修女
And to keep the sisters away from you.
因为她们抱有远大理想
'Cause they can have a pack mentality.
最终 是一股正气
Ultimately, this is gonna be a very positive influence.
每天道德地活着 为上帝服务
Living ethically every day, serving God.
那真的会巩固你的灵魂
It's really gonna fortify your soul.
你是对的 我想我可以学到很多
Yeah, you're right. I think I can learn a lot
通过看着修女们和周围的人
by watching the sisters and everyone around,
他们看起来很有道德
who seem very ethical and, yeah.
干杯
Cheers.
其实我是想问你
Actually, I was gonna ask you, is it...
我们继续喝圣酒有问题吗?
Is it all right that we keep drinking the sacramental wine?
我祝福过 所以
Well, I blessed it, so...
你祝福了 所以... - 我的意思是
You blessed it, so it's... - I mean,
不要告诉别人 但是
don't mention it to anyone else, but...
我怎么能?我又聋又哑 记得吗?
How could I? I'm deaf and mute, remember?
你好 - 嗨
Hi. - Hi.
你不会要去睡觉吧?
You're not going to bed, are you?
不
No.
你有喝的吗?
Do you have anything to drink?
你想要什么?
What do you want?
妥玛索神父把橱柜上锁了
Father Tommasso left the ambry unlocked.
你好 我叫玛塔
Hi. I'm Marta.
她是我儿时的朋友
She's my childhood friend.
儿时的朋友 - 我们一起长大的
Yeah, yeah, childhood friend. - We grew up together.
你喝醉了吗?
Are you drunk?
不
No. And...
那你应该多喝点
Then you should have more.
你的房间真漂亮
Your room's gorgeous.
我爸爸给我的
Yeah. My dad got it for me.
为什么这么大?比其他房间大得多
Why is it so big? It's a lot bigger than your room.
是吗?
Is it?
我从没进过你的房间
I've never been in your room.
你来过
Yes, you have.
不
No.
别笑
Don't laugh.
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
没什么 回床上去
Nothing. Go back to bed.
我睡不着 你太吵了 - 滚出去
I can't sleep! You're too loud! - Get outta here!
快他妈的进来
Get the fuck in here!
你在这里干什么?
What are you doing here?
他妈的闭嘴 - 你在干什么?
Shut the fuck up. - What are you doing?
你是谁?
Who... Who are you?
你好 - 那是玛塔
Hi. - That's Marta.
我叫玛塔
I'm Marta.
你有口音 你从哪儿来?南方?
You have an accent. Where are you from? The south?
上帝 - 你是从翁布里亚来的吗?
Oh, my God. - Are you from Umbria?
不 她在说什么?
No. What's she talking about?
我跟你口音一样 - 她是本地的
I sound just like you. - No. She's from here.
你不是从格塔纳纳来的 - 她是本地人
You're not from Gartagnana. - Yes, she is.
你听起来不像格塔纳纳口音
You do not sound like you're from Gartagnana.
你在喝圣酒吗?
Are you drinking the sacramental wine?
是的 - 不
Yes. - No.
妥玛索神父一直在喝酒
Father Tommasso drinks it all the time. - I'm gonna tell Mother Marea.
我要告诉玛利亚院长
I'm gonna tell Mother Marea.
你为什么总是揭发别人?
Why are you always telling on people?
你为什么要掐我?
Why are you choking me?
闭嘴 就喝点吧
Yeah, shut up. Just drink a little bit of it.
亚历山大修女要你喝酒
Sister Alessandra wants you to drink.
吉尼芙拉 没事的
Ginevra, it's fine.
人生没有什么要紧的 我们都会死的
Nothing matters in life. We're all gonna die.
可怕的事情一直在发生
Terrible things are happening all the time.
这里不许有访客
You're not allowed to have visitors here.
你不被允许... - 享受这一刻吧
You're not allowed... - Just enjoy this moment...
我们都会死的
We're all gonna die.
只是喝点酒
And just drink a little wine.
但我们不会惹麻烦吧? - 去吧
But we're not gonna get in trouble? - Do it.
喝吧
Do it.
喔
Whoo!
味道不好 太糟糕了
Oh, that tastes bad. That's bad.
我想里面有沙子
I think there was sand in it.
你们真的从来没有
Is it true that you've never...
被男人碰过 或碰过男人?
Been touched by a man, or touched a man?
没有
No.
从来没有?
Never?
从来没有
No, never.
我为你感到难过 你知道这是什么感觉吗?
I feel sad for you. Do you ever wonder what it's like?
怎么?真的很棒吗?
Why? Is it really so great?
这是世界上最大的乐趣
It's the greatest pleasure on Earth.
真的?
Really? - Mmm.
天哪 你绝不知道
Oh, my God, you have no idea.
事实上 它是如此之好 我听说有女人
In fact, it's so good that I've heard of women
从植物颠茄提取药剂
(一种瞳孔放大剂)
who make this potion out of this plant belladonna
只是为了勾引男人
just to seduce men.
我们不能这么做 因为会被关起来
We can't do it, 'cause we would get locked up.
这是致命的罪过 我们会进不了天堂的
Yeah, it's a mortal sin. We wouldn't get into Heaven.
致命的罪过
It's a mortal sin.
那你更不应该这么做
Yeah, then you probably shouldn't do it.
也许不该这么做
Probably shouldn't do it.
其实无所谓 因为我们永远都不会知道
Doesn't really matter, anyway, 'cause we're never gonna know that.
从来没有要紧的事
Nothing matters.
你真的是从格塔纳纳来的吗?
Are you really from Gartagnana?
我才是
Yeah. I am.
嗨 小家伙
Hi, little one.
我感觉不舒服
I don't feel well.
我感觉不舒服 - 是因为太紧了
I don't feel well. - Yeah, it's 'cause this is too tight.
不
No...
我们只是
Yeah, let's just...
我该走了
I should go. I should go.
好吧 我很抱歉
Okay. No, I'm sorry.
对不起 但是
I'm sorry! But what is...
不 这是我的房间
Oh, no, it's my room.
这是我的房间
This is my room.
这是你的房间
Yeah, it's your room.
对不起 - 没关系
I'm sorry. - It's okay.
对不起 我没有
I'm sorry. I don't...
你好
Hi. Um...
Hi.
你好
我为你做了这个
I made this for you.
给你的 我给你看看
For you, yes. Let me show you.
你可以
You can, um, sort of...
只是为了谢谢
It says thank you, just for...
那天我跟你说话
Just letting me talk to you the other day.
我说得太疯狂了
I talk so crazy, I know.
我的意思是 你不能听到我的话
I mean, you know, you can't, you know, hear me.
你需要帮助吗?
Do you need help? Do you need help?
我只是
I just...
好吧 这对你有帮助吗?
Okay. Is that help for you?
你就是这样做的吗?
Yeah. Is that how you do it?
好
Okay. Okay.
我太脏了
Oh, I'm so dirty.
太热了
It's so warm.
这里太热了
It's so hot out here.
只需要
Just have to...
好多了
That's better.
抱歉
Sorry.
你是对的
You're right. You're right.
太快了
That's too fast.
太快了 我们应该停止
That's too fast. We should stop.
抱歉
Sorry.
抱歉 对不起
Sorry. I'm sorry.
好吧
Okay.
再见
Bye.
荣耀归与神
Glory to God in the highest,
世上 和平只给善意的人
and on Earth, peace to people of good will.
我们赞美你 我们祝福你
We praise you. We bless you.
我们崇拜你 我们赞美你
We adore you. We glorify you.
我们感谢您的伟大荣耀 主啊 上帝
We give you thanks for your great glory, Lord God.
神啊 全能的天父啊
Heavenly King, O God, Almighty Father...
昨晚很好
Last night was nice.
你累了吗?
Are you tired?
是
Yeah.
我也是
Yeah, me too.
你感觉还好吧?
You feel okay?
我感觉不舒服
No, I don't feel good.
我很开心
I had fun.
我说我感觉不舒服 你能不能别再说了?
I said I don't feel good. Can you please stop talking?
好吧
Well, okay.
嗨 女士们
Hi, ladies.
你们在这里干什么?
What are you doing here?
我刚好路过
Um, I was just in the neighborhood.
什么?
What?
我开玩笑的
I'm kidding.
我的面纱有点脏了
No, my veil just got a little dirty,
我知道你们俩在这里
and I knew you girls were here,
我想我来看看
and I thought I'd come visit
和你们一起洗
and wash it with you guys.
你要洗自己的面纱?
You're gonna wash your own veil?
为什么不呢?
Yeah. Why not?
你什么都不洗的
You never wash anything.
昨晚不是很有趣吗?
Wasn't last night so fun?
你的面纱怎么会这么脏?
How'd your veil get so dirty?
我刚才在花园里
Well, earlier I was in the garden,
新来的杂工在那里挖沟
and the new handyman was there digging a ditch,
我只是想帮他
and I just thought I'd help him out.
你挖沟?
You dug a ditch?
实际上 真的很有趣
It was actually... It was really fun.
我该怎么办?
So, what do I do?
只需要泡在水里?
Do I just dip it in the... In the water?
这里
It's so... Ooh, it's...
这里真的很脏
It's really dirty over here.
首先你把它放进水里
First you put it in the water,
然后你放在灰碗里
and then you bring it over to the bowl that has the ash.
放进去 然后把灰撒在上面
And you put it in the bowl, and you put the ash on top of it,
然后过一天
and then you let it sit for a day.
第二天回来
So then tomorrow, you would come back
从碗里拿出来
and take it out of the bowl,
水里冲洗一下
and then you rinse it really well in the water...
然后拧干
And then you wring it out,
挂在杆子上
and then you hang it up on the line.
听起来 你真的很擅长
Sounds like you are really good at this...
所以 也许我...
So, maybe I'll just...
还是留给你好了
I'll leave it here with you.
太棒了
This was great.
谢谢 再见 姑娘们
Thank you. Bye, you guys.
再见
Bye.
我想我会洗到死的
Guess I would have ended up washing this eventually.
这个也洗掉
Here. Finish this.
我得去把地窖收拾一下
I have to go tidy up the cellar.
在这里
Here it is.
应该够了
Yeah, there should be enough here.
费尔南达修女?
Sister Fernanda?
记住不要放进嘴里
Just have to remember not to get this in your mouth, okay?
我知道
I know.
脱掉修女装
Take off the nun thing.
你会撒的到处都是
You'll get it all over it.
准备好了吗? -嗯
Okay, you ready? - Yeah.
好吧
All right.
来吧
Go for it.
只是
Just going to...
让你看起来
Make you look a little more...
更漂亮点
Presentable.
照我说的做
Do exactly what I tell you to do.
确保他看到你的眼睛
Make sure he sees your eyes.
好的 吻他
Okay, kiss him.
吻他
Kiss him.
快
Come on.
好 靠近点
Okay, get closer.
小心刀子
Careful with the knife.
全含进去
Take it all in.
好
Okay.
到他上面去
Get on top of him.
把你的性器顶在他胃部
Push your sex into his stomach.
好了
All right.
他能干
He'll do.
你们在里面做什么?
What were you doing in there?
你好
Hi.
你从哪里来?
Where'd you come from?
我只是在摘根菜
I was just picking root vegetables.
你真的是从格塔纳纳来的吗?
Are you really from Gartagnana?
对 我真的来自格塔纳纳
Yes, I'm really from Gartagnana.
你为什么一直问我?
Why do you keep asking me?
你问过我 25次了
You've asked me, like, 25...
你真烦人
You are the most annoying!
你不理我了吗?
Are you ignoring me?
不
No.
我觉得你不理我了 - 我没有
I feel like you're ignoring me. - I'm not.
我能问你一个问题吗?
Can I ask you a question?
说
Yes.
昨晚对你有什么意义吗?
Did last night mean anything to you?
没有
No.
我们只是喝醉了 玩得很开心
We were just drunk and having fun.
忘记了吧
Forget about it.
好吧
All right.
马赛托
Masseto, Masseto, Masseto.
我实际上
I'm actually...
我现在很好
I'm all right right now.
好吧
Oh, all right.
过得怎么样?
How's it going?
今天是个好日子
It was a good day.
我
Yeah, I um...
我不知道 我可以
I don't know. I can kind of...
我能在这里待一阵子
I can kind of picture myself maybe being here a while.
真的?你能留下来?
Really? You think you could stay on?
只要你允许
If you'd have me, yeah.
开什么玩笑?
Are you kidding?
这将解决很多问题
That would solve a lot of problems.
和修女们怎么样?还行吗?
And how's it going with the sisters? That's all right?
我觉得她们在为我热身
I think they're kind of warming up to me.
很好 没有过分?
Good. Good, good. Not too much?
不 绝对
No. Definitely...
绝对没有过分
Definitely not too much.
刚刚好的感觉
It's the right amount, feels like.
不管怎样 让我们举杯吧
Anyway, let's have a toast,
快速敬酒
just a quick toast...
然后忏悔
And then maybe head over to confession.
就像我们一直那样
Yeah. - You know, like we do.
我想今晚不用 我感觉有点累
I think I'm good tonight, just 'cause I'm gonna... Feeling a little tired.
今天真是漫长的一天 - 好的
It's been a long day. - All right, yeah.
但把酒倒回去 要倒霉的
It's bad luck to put it back in the pitcher, though...
所以 我们就喝这点 然后...
So, let's just have this one, and then...
你好?
Hello?
你独自一人吗?
Are you alone?
当然 - 好像听到有人
Of course. - I thought I heard someone.
不 我在自言自语
No, no, no. I was talking to myself.
我们出去走会儿
Let's take a little walk.
巴托洛梅奥主教 你好
Bishop Bartolomeo, hello.
妥玛索神父
Father Tommasso.
啊 很高兴见到你
Ah, it's good to see you.
谢谢
Thank you.
请进 进来 - 你好
Come in. Come in. Come in. - Hello.
我来拿 你一定累坏了
Here. Let me take this. You must be exhausted.
非常累 很长的旅程
Very tired, very long trip.
见到你真好
So good to see you.
我也很高兴见到你
So good to see you, too.
有点出乎意料
Somewhat unexpected.
看起来不错
Looks great.
都准备好了
We'll get it together for you.
我相信你们
Oh, yes, I'm sure you will.
妈的
Oh, shit!
笃笃笃 她们不在这里吗?
Knock-knock. Are they not here?
她们消失了
They disappeared. - Oh.
你认识亚历山大·伊拉里欧的女儿吗?
And you know Alessandra, Ilario's daughter?
当然是伊拉里欧的女儿
Ilario's daughter, of course.
你好
Hi.
他的生意目前不太好 - 太糟糕了
His business is not doing very well at the moment. - Oh, that's terrible.
很抱歉这么说
Sorry to say, yeah.
我想要一条
I want one of those.
我们可以给你一条
We can get you one.
都是你的
Yes, it's yours, it's yours!
谢谢你 亚历山大修女 - 谢谢
Thank you, Sister Alessandra. - Thank you.
很高兴见到你 - 感谢您的时间
Nice to see you. - We appreciate your time.
"我们都去了野外"
And we all went out to the field
"并致力于单向之路"
and worked on a single plot.
我明白你的意思
I see your point,
但我想让你关注此处
but I'd like you to focus here.
但我善于爬山
No, but I'm fine with March.
2月份 如何卖纺织品的?
In February, how did you sell textiles before they were sold?
我喜欢你说的话 如果你...
I like what you're saying, and if you...
不过是爬山 我善于爬山
No. But this is March. I'm fine with March.
玛利亚院长 我要和你谈谈费尔南达修女
Mother Marea, I need to talk to you about Sister Fernanda.
她没事吧? -  她的行为非常可疑
Is she all right? - Well, she's acting very suspicious.
我有些你想知道的事情
And I've learned some things I think you'd want to know.
她不是说那头驴逃走了吗?
You know how she's been saying that the donkey escaped?
不是逃跑 - 好吧 现在不是时候
It's not escaping. - Okay, this is not the right time.
她一直在撒谎
She's been lying about it the whole time.
你会想知道的
She's lying about it. You'll want to know about it.
我很抱歉 - 你看到这些数字了吗?
I'm so sorry about that. - Have you seen these numbers? Who...
我一般负责监督
I supervise in general...
数字 但...
The numbers, but...
费尔南达有事情
There's something going on with Fernanda.
她说她要去...
She said that she was going...
修女 我在问 请小声一点 - 她根本不在那里
Sister, I'm asking, please keep your voice down. - She wasn't there!
她显然在撒谎 她有个朋友过来
- She was clearly lying. She had a friend over,
喝了酒
and she drank alcohol.
她还不睡觉 我整晚都在听她说话 - 没说那么多...
She's staying up! I hear her up all night. - Don't talk so much...
驴子逃走的事 她显然是在骗人
She's clearly lying about the donkey escaping.
她为什么要拿驴子撒谎?
Why would she lie about the donkey?
我不知道她为什么撒谎 但我检查了围墙
I don't know why she's lying, but I checked the walls,
检查了所有的大门
and I checked all of the gates.
那头驴是不可能逃走的
There's no way that donkey's escaping.
我认为需要别人照顾驴子
I think that donkey needs someone else to take care of her.
我可以照顾她
I can take care of her.
我会考虑的
I will consider it.
谢谢 院长 - 我们稍后再讨论这个问题
Thank you, Mother. - We'll discuss this later.
这不是很棒吗 修女们?
Isn't that amazing, Sisters?
那朵玫瑰有能力
That Rose had the ability
预测弗雷德里克二世死亡的确切日期
to predict the exact day of the death of Frederick II.
我认为我们都有能力与神紧密联系
I think we all have this ability to connect deeply with God.
我分享这个故事 因为我们不总是听从上帝
I share the story, because we don't always listen to God.
嘿
Hey!
这是怎么回事?
What's going on?
你会说话?
You can speak?
不
No, no. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
我听到了
I heard you. I heard you!
告诉我现在怎么回事
Tell me what's going on right now,
否则我会告诉大家 你一直在耍我们
or I'm gonna tell everyone here that you've been tricking us!
好了 对不起
All right, all right, all right. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
我不应该和你说话
I'm not supposed to talk to you.
你不应该和我说话?
You're not supposed to talk to me?
那是什么意思?
What does that even mean?
有人吗
Hello? Hello?
趴下 - 你能听到我吗?
Get down. Get down. - Can you hear me?
你能听到我说话吗?你好?
Can you hear me? Hello?
不 你听不到
No, you can't hear me.
你能听到我的想法吗?
Can you hear my thoughts?
因为我能听到你的想法
'Cause I can hear your thoughts.
我能听到你的想法
I can hear your thoughts.
你好
Hi.
这感觉好不同
This feels different.
我想我更喜欢和女孩上床
I think I like sex with girls.
我从没告诉过任何人
I never told anyone.
我有很多秘密 我是犹太人
I have lots of secrets. I'm Jewish.
没人知道 但现在你知道了
Nobody knows, but now you know.
但你不知道 因为你无法...
But you don't know, 'cause you can't...
天使来了
There's the angels.
你看到天使了吗?
Do you see the angels?
我看到了 我听到了
I see the... Oh, I hear 'em. I hear 'em.
她们知道我在这里
Oh, they know. They know I'm here. They know I'm here.
天啊 好
Oh, God. Okay.
你在这里干什么?
What are you doing here?
我是来核查干草的 嘘
I'm just looking through the hay. Shh!
费尔南达 你他妈的到底怎么了?
Fernanda! - What the fuck is wrong with you?
为什么你脸上都是血?
Why is there blood all over your face?
别挡我的路
Get out of my way!
费尔南达?费尔南达?
Fernanda? Fernanda?
那边 快 他们把驴带走了
Over there. Come on. They have the donkey.
天啊 你没事吧?
Oh, jeez. Are you okay?
你没事吧?
Are you okay?
我要吐了
I'm gonna throw up.
好了 吐出来
Okay, okay, okay. Let it out.
我不会吐了
I'm not gonna throw up.
好的
Okay, okay.
我们继续走
Let's keep moving. We're gonna keep going.
继续前进 - 我好热 为什么我这么热?
Keep going. - I'm so hot. Why am I so hot?
我不知道 - 我好渴
I don't know. - Oh, I'm so thirsty.
得继续走
Gotta keep going.
什么亮光?看亮光
What is the lights? Look at the lights.
这是什么
What is it...
我服了颠茄素 - 什么?
I took the belladonna. I took the belladonna. - What?
她做了爱 所以我也要做爱
She had it. She had the sex, and so I was gonna have the sex.
所以我提取了颠茄 所以我可以做爱
So I did belladonna so I could have the sex...
女巫
Witches.
她们是女巫
They're witches!
他闹得很大声
He's making a lot of noise.
没关系 他是个聋哑
It's okay. He's a deaf-mute.
也许我们该把他堵嘴
Yeah, well, maybe we should gag him.
没有意义 他不能说话
There's no point. He can't talk.
闭嘴
Shut up.
吉尼芙拉 不
Ginevra, no.
吉尼芙拉 回来
Ginevra, come back here.
吉尼芙拉 快回来
Ginevra, get back here!
停下
Stop!
女神拥抱过的 便可放置于此
For so it was placed when the goddess embraced.
有角的上帝 上帝教会她话语
The horned lord, our god who taught her the word.
鼓舞了子宫 征服了坟墓
Which quickened the womb and conquered the tomb.
长矛到圣杯 灵魂到肉体
Lance to grail, spirit to flesh,
太阳到月球
sun to moon.
你的熊熊大火永远只为雄性
Forever your flame is the male.
别杀我 求你了
Don't fucking kill me. No, don't, please.
别杀我 我会做任何事
Don't fucking kill me! I'll do anything, please!
我们治好了他 - 绝无可能
We cured him. - There's absolutely no way.
他就是个聋哑
I'm telling you, he was a deaf-mute.
你什么都不知道 这是生育仪式
You know nothing. This is a fertility ritual.
我叫你堵他嘴的
You know, I told you to gag him.
下次注意听好
It'll be great if you just listen next time.
好
Okay.
你们都在看什么?
What are you all looking at?
为什么看着我?
Why are you looking at me?
她在这里做什么?
What is she doing here?
什么?
What?
吉尼芙拉
Ginevra!
冷静 把图腾放下
Calm down. Put the totem down!
你不属于这里
You do not belong here!
把它给我
Give it to me.
你不属于这里
You don't belong here!
不 - 你不属于这里
No, No. - You don't belong!
肉体的灵魂 太阳到月亮
Spirit to flesh, sun to moon.
安静
Quiet.
费尔南达 住手
Fernanda! Stop this!
天啊 你在这里干什么?
God, what are you doing here?
我不会让你杀了他的
I won't let you kill him!
住手 亚历山大 我要和他做爱
Stop it, Alessandra! I need to have sex with him!
你为什么
Why are you...
你为什么在这里?
Why are you even here?
你不知道力量...
You don't know the powers of...
你是女巫?这太疯狂了
You're a witch? This is crazy!
你一直在骗我们?
And you were lying to us this whole time?
解释一下
Yes, explain yourself!
好了
All right, all right, all right.
这些人想杀我
These people, they want to kill me,
然后我就跑了
and I went on the run...
这是我的驴
This is my donkey!
她想带走我的驴
She's trying to take my donkey.
我们得去找她 - 她失控了
We have to get her. She's out of control.
好了 让我们... - 已经够用刀子了
All right, let's... - Enough with the knife already.
那该死的婊子
That fucking bitch.
你们需要知道发生了什么
You need to know what's going on!
你们要知道
You need to know!
醒来
Wake up!
醒来 醒来
Wake up! Wake up!
你们需要知道发生了什么事
You need to know what's going on!
等一下 我马上就到
Just a minute. I'll be right there.
你在做什么?这是半夜 - 她们是女巫
What are you doing? It's the middle of the night! - They're witches!
她们是女巫
They're witches!
女巫啊
You need to know about the witches!
她们就在树林里
They're out there in the woods!
把你的衣服穿上 - 费尔南达 她的朋友是女巫
Put your clothes on. - Fernanda's a witch, her friend's a witch!
冷静 - 她们都在外面 巴托洛梅奥神父
Calm down! - They're all out there! Father Bartolomeo,
你得知道有女巫
you need to know. There are witches...
她是个女巫
She's a witch! She is a witch!
我不是女巫 - 停止
I am not a witch! - Stop!
你只是在嫉妒 - 不 我不是
You're just jealous. - No, I am not!
你为什么要穿冬天的袍子
Why are you wearing your winter habit?
我先看到他的 - 为什么这里有杂工?
I saw him first. - Why is the handyman here?
你是什么意思 你先看到他的?你根本不喜欢男人
What do you mean, you saw him first? You don't even like men!
你喜欢女人
You're sexually attracted to women.
我对男人有性吸引力
I am sexually attracted to men.
什么? - 我和他上床了
What? - I had sex with him!
你是基督的新妇 - 你没有和他做爱
You are a bride of Christ! - You did not have sex with him.
你只是在他身上打滚 - 你也和他上床了- 闭嘴
You were just writhing around on him.You had sex with him, too. - Stop.
{\move(750,20,-250,20)\fnMicrosoft YaHei\fs12\b1\alpha&H25\q2\bord2\1c&HFFFFFF&\1a&H00&\3c&H000000&}澳门新葡京娱乐城 www.416.net 日本AV女优荷官现场发牌，百家乐日送80万，以小搏大，紧张刺激，100万提款30秒火速到账，官方直营，大额无忧！！
你怎么敢?主教 我没有做爱 - 我说的是实话
How dare you? Bishop, I did not have sex. - I'm telling the truth.
你为什么告密?
Why are you a tattletale, huh?
我知道你在做什么 她现在是我的驴
I know what you're doing and she's my donkey now!
不要谈论我的驴
Don't talk about my donkey.
我现在负责驴子
I am on donkey duty now!
她有什么毛病?
What is wrong with her?
她嗑药了
She is on drugs!
她告诉我 她今晚服用颠茄素
She told me she took belladonna tonight,
她和女巫在树林里裸体跳舞
and she's been dancing around naked in the woods with witches.
她是个犹太人
And she's a Jew!
我不是犹太人
I am not a Jew!
玛利亚修女
Sister Marea!
别说话了
Stop talking.
我不是犹太人
I am not a Jew!
闭嘴
Yes! Stop. Stop.
玛利亚修女  醒来
Sister Marea! Sister Marea! Wake up!
我不是犹太人
I'm not a Jew. I'm not a Jew.
出来吧 看看这个
Come out here. Look at this.
我在睡觉
I was sleeping!
完全混乱 - 对不起
Complete chaos! - I'm sorry.
大家都醒了 - 你脸上是什么?
Everyone's awake. - What's on your face?
现在是半夜 楼下有一头驴
It's the middle of the night. There's a donkey downstairs.
为什么你的头上有裤子?
Why do you have pants on your head?
都请停下
Okay, just please stop!
我可以解释一切好吗?都是我的错
I can explain everything, all right? It's all my fault.
我以为你不会说话
I thought you couldn't speak!
他会说话
He can speak.
他会说话 - 我以为你是个聋哑
Yeah, he can talk. - I thought you were a deaf-mute!
这是个奇迹
It's a miracle.
开始审裁
We're going to begin the tribunal.
吉尼芙拉修女 这是你的罪过
Sister Ginevra, these are your sins.
吸食毒品
Ingestion of drugs,
和一个女人躺在一起
lying with a woman,
没有受洗
not being baptized.
没有受洗?
Not being baptized?
所以成就了你现在的样子
That's what makes you what you are.
你不能...根本不应进修道院的门
You can't... You shouldn't even be coming through those doors!
好管闲事 谈吐猥亵
Being a busybody, filthy conversation...
徒劳吵闹 酗酒
Vain jangling, drinking...
吃血
Eating blood.
你觉得我以前写过"吃血"吗?
Do you think I've ever written down "Eating blood" before?
我在哪里?
Where am I?
嫉妒 通奸 同性恋
Envy, fornication, homosexuality...
和睡女人是一个意思
That's the same as lying with a woman,
暂且不提
but we separate those.
好色 陶醉
Lustfulness, reveling,
伤害了你的心
mischief in your heart.
这是我见过的最长的单子
That's the longest list I've ever had...
为罪恶
For sins.
请宽恕我
Please have mercy on me.
为了惩罚你
For your punishment,
我要你斋戒一年
I'm going to have you fast for one year.
OK
Okay.
我还没有解释 所以这不OK - OK
I didn't explain it yet, so it's not okay. - Okay.
人不吃 会死的
Because a human being can't live on not eating.
不 - 我不是说你整整一年都不吃东西
No. - I don't mean you're not gonna eat for a whole year.
你只有白天一顿饭
You just pick a meal in the day
然后跳过一顿 - 好的
and skip it. - Okay.
说的是午餐 每天你都得跳过午餐
So, say, it's lunch. Every day, you've got to skip lunch.
是 - 那算什么餐?
Yes. - And what meal is that?
呃
Uh...
根据你的建议 我不吃午饭了
Based on your suggestion, I'll skip lunch.
这不是我的建议
It's not my suggestion.
你必须感受到罪恶
You have to feel the sin.
我能感觉到午餐
I can feel lunch.
亚历山大修女
Sister Alessandra.
你知道的
You know...
我是你父亲的朋友
I'm friends with your father,
他的女儿竟然这样?
and now his daughter is doing this?
对不起 我很抱歉
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
真丢人
It's embarrassing.
我很尴尬 你觉得他会有什么感觉?
For me, I'm embarrassed. How do you think he's gonna feel when he knows this?
别告诉我父亲
Please don't tell my father.
没必要告诉我父亲 - 他是教会的赞助人
There's no need to tell my father. - He's a patron of the church,
最大的一个
one of the biggest.
这个地方完全失修 正在崩溃
And this place is completely in disrepair. It's falling apart.
看起来像富利卡亚的谷仓
It looks like a barn in Filicaia.
你去过那里吗?
Have you been there?
真恶心 - 太恶心了
It's disgusting. - It's disgusting!
请不要这么说
Please, please don't say that.
我想把这个地方叫做小富利卡亚
I think I want to call this place Little Filicaia.
不 求你了 - 我会的
No, please. - I might.
费尔南达修女 这是你的罪过
Sister Fernanda, these are your sins.
判教
Apostasy,
异端
heresy,
粗言秽语 - 这只是我的声调
abusive language... - It's just the tone of my voice.
同性恋
Homosexuality...
狂欢 巫术
Revelings, witchcraft.
你瞥眼睛了吗?
Did you roll your eyes?
没有
No.
你在瞥眼睛
You were rolling your eyes.
玛利亚修女 我不知道该说什么
Sister Marea, I don't know what to say.
我很震惊
I am shocked.
淫乱?寻欢作乐?
Fornication? Living in pleasure?
你 玛利亚修女 你
You, Sister Marea, you.
爱俗世?
Loving the world?
你为什么呆在这里?
Why don't you just stay here?
你为什么不留在你爱的俗世里?
Why don't you stay in this world that you love so much?
因为好玩吗?
Isn't it fun?
你有什么要说的吗?
Do you have anything to say?
我很抱歉 教宗阁下
I'm so sorry, Your Holiness.
你在乎吗?
Do you care?
只因完全缺乏...
It's just complete lack of...
你们在互相微笑吗?
Are you guys smiling at each other?
你们能有片刻不看彼此?
Can you have a moment to not look at each other?
你们都失控了
You're both out of control.
妥玛索神父
Father Tommasso...
我都不知道从何说起
I don't even know where to begin.
我请求你的宽恕
I ask your forgiveness...
我祈求上帝的宽恕
And I ask God's forgiveness
因为这群牧羊人的失败
for failing as the shepherd of this flock.
我请求你不要因为我的过失 而惩罚修道院修女
I only ask that you please not punish the sisters of this convent for my failings.
玛利亚
Marea.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
他夺走了我的神职
He's taken away my priesthood.
我要去圣迪比亚吉奥当和尚
I have to go to San Biagio and become a monk.
我很抱歉把你拖下水
I'm so sorry for dragging you into this.
你是个好女人 玛利亚
You're a good woman. You're a good woman, Marea.
我应该... - 你到底在干什么?
I should... - What the hell are you doing?
快离开这里
Get outta here!
你刚才在里面不是才忏悔过吗?
You were just crying in there?
你怎么了?
What's wrong with you?
和弗朗西丝卡躺在一起值得吗?
Was lying with Francesca worth it?
我真的不想谈这个
I really don't want to talk about it.
那胸呢? - 非常丰盈
What about that bosom? Very ample.
超级丰盈 而且是布鲁诺的妻子
Super ample, plus it's Bruno's wife,
所以必须是如此风骚
so it had to be so intense.
你们能不能别再说了?
Can you guys please stop talking?
你听说她的事了 对吧?
You heard what happened to her, right?
没有 我怎么会听到?
No. How could I have heard?
"在寒冷的季末
"At the end of the cold season,
沿着树枝
"when along the branch
浪涌的汁液 复苏了金雀花和石楠花
"surges the sap that revives the broom and heather.
值桃树开花 青蛙在水池里歌唱
"When the peach trees blossom and the frog sings in the pool
柳树和老树萌出新芽
"and the willow and elder grow,
而当干燥的月份到来
"as I see the dry months come,
我在大果园
"I concern myself with a large orchard
那里有许多美丽的树苗
"where there are beautiful saplings in many places.
嫁接繁茂  果实累累
(赤裸裸的暗喻)
"The grafts are large, and the fruit fleshy
而它们本该已经腐烂
"on those that should be the worst.
然而 那些看起来如苹果般的花朵
"And the blossoms look like those of apples."
但是 当该结果的时候
"But when the fruit comes,
却一无所有 徒留柳树和老树
"it is nothing but willow and elder.
"那是因为始乱终弃"
"And since the head is empty, the members at the ends are in pain."
你打扫完地窖了吗?
Did you finish cleaning the cellar?
是 都完成了
Yeah, all done.
是不是很烦人?
Isn't it so annoying?
真烦人 - 我告诉过你了
So annoying. - I told you.
我知道
I know.
抱歉 我告密了你
Sorry I told on you.
对不起 我告诉了玛利亚院长
Sorry that I told Mother Marea every time I thought
每次我觉得有些事情不对劲的时候
something wasn't right or weird.
抱歉我毁了你的仪式
Sorry I ruined your ritual.
很抱歉 我没告诉你我是个女巫
I'm sorry I didn't tell you I was a witch.
但说实话
But honestly,
我想最终 我能把你们都变成女巫
I thought eventually I could turn you all into witches,
你会加入我的集会 但我知道这听起来很愚蠢
and you'd join my coven, but I know that sounds stupid.
你真的认为我会做女巫?
You really think I could be a witch?
是
Yeah.
你觉得她们会杀了他吗?
Do you think they're gonna kill him?
我不知道最近乔瓦尼怎么样了
I don't know what's going on with Giovanni lately.
你注意到她们为士兵们提供的胡萝卜都软趴趴的吗?
Have you noticed the carrots they're serving the soldiers are mushier?
我昨天也说了同样的话
I was saying the same thing yesterday.
我无所谓 如果胡萝卜外面都黏糊糊的
(赤裸裸的暗喻)
I would even be okay if they were mushy on the outside
里面很脆 我并不需要从里到外的脆
and crispy on the inside. I don't need, like, a full crisp, but...
可能有点伤感 胡萝卜有点软对我不是问题
It could be a little mushy. I'm fine with a little mush.
因为这是胡萝卜布丁
'Cause this is basically carrot pudding.
他在哪?
Where is he?
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
对不起 让你久等了 我去了萨尔扎那
I'm sorry to keep you waiting. I've been in Sarzana
和我新娘的家人见面
meeting with the family of my new bride.
美丽的年轻女士
Beautiful young lady
看起来她可能会很忠诚
who seems like she might be up to fidelity.
想象一下
Imagine that.
一旦她进入青春期
Once she hits puberty.
谢谢你帮我一个大忙
I have to thank you for doing me an incredible favor.
我的妻子隐瞒了她的祖先
My wife, who had hidden her Guelph ancestry,
结果是
turned out to be
相当的贫瘠的阴道
quite the barren twat.
你给了我所有的理由
And you've given me every reason
用野猪和狗把她封印在墙上
to seal her up in a wall with a boar and a dog.
我有个好消息
I've got some good news
还有一些坏消息
and some bad news.
你喜欢哪一个?
Which would you like first?
我不在乎
I don't care.
好消息是我会让你活很久
The good news is I'm going to keep you alive for as long as I can.
听起来很愉快 坏消息是
It sounds cheery. The bad news is
这只是为了让我给你更多的痛苦...
it's only so that I can inflict as much pain
和堕落 因为我要折磨你的肉体
and degradation as I torture your flesh.
我很难确定
I'm having a hard time determining
我最喜欢哪个酷刑
which of my favorite torture methods
对你先来一套
to start with upon you.
有拇指夹 我有一个凯瑟琳车轮
Got the thumbscrew. I have a Catherine wheel.
我后面有个架子
I have a rack out back.
这里占用了太多的空间
It was taking up too much space in here,
但仍然功能齐全
but still fully functional.
有个新的刑具 叫做鼠盒
There's a new one called the rat box
来自西西里
just in from Sicily.
鼠盒 不被混淆于
The rat box, not to be confused with
我所说的我老婆的女人私密区
what I call my wife's private area
也就是你参观过地方
after you'd been to visit.
这是一只开孔的鼠盒
It's a box of rats with one open side
放在你的腹部
placed against your abdomen.
我在盒子的另一边点火
I light a fire on the other side of the box,
让老鼠们在试图逃跑的时候
so that the rats, in their attempts to escape,
会钻过你的肠子
burrow through your guts.
无论如何 会有很多的乐趣
Anyway, we'll have a lot of fun together
在未来的日子里 也许是几周
in the coming days and maybe weeks,
取决于你有多强硬
depending on how tough you are.
你哪儿也去不了
Don't go anywhere.
妈的
Shit.
根本没有好消息
There was no good news in that at all.
嘿  我真的
Hey, um... I'd actually...
如果你们现在让我出去 我会很感激的
I'd really appreciate it if you guys let me out now.
不能这样对我们
Can't do that to us.
拜托 - 设身处地
Please. - It's a tough position.
我们是朋友 好吗?
Hey, hey, we're friends, all right?
你也不想在这里
You don't want to be here either.
让我出去 我们会逃跑的
Just let me out. We'll make a run for it.
我 - 我们不能
I... - We can't.
他什么都逃不开
He can't make a run for anything.
如果我死了 那是你的良心
If I die, that's on your conscience.
你不想内疚地活着
You don't want to live with that.
求你
Please.
什么
What... Is...
好 你要快点行动
Okay. You're gonna have to move quick,
特别是在护城河附近
especially around the moat.
外面的守卫真的很嗜血
The guards out there have a real thirst for blood.
当然 非常感谢
Yes, of course. Thank you so much.
好了 我放开了 - 好的
Okay, here I go. - Okay.
我要解开你的锁
I'm unlocking you.
你搞什么...
What are you...
有一只蜡烛乌龟
There's a turtle with a candle on it!
真的?
Really?
等等 别离开我
Wait, wait, wait! Don't leave me!
嘿 你要去哪里?别离开我
Hey, where are you going? Don't leave me!
快 站住 你这狗屎
Come on! Just please. Stop, you shits!
我们看看乌龟要做什么 - 妈的
Let's see what he does. - Shit.
你在这里干什么?
What are you doing here?
我们要把你弄出去 - 你好
We're getting you out. Hi.
快
Come on!
快 快
Come on. Come on.
快
Whoa, whoa. Come on!
没事的 我会给你的
No, no, it's okay. I'm giving it to you.
你可以相信我们
You can trust us.
我们在拯救你
We're rescuing you!
我绣了这个娃娃放在你的房间
I embroidered this doll to put in your place.
我们给你带来了暗夜袍子 让你隐于黑夜
We brought you a lunar habit to hide you in the night.
我们想把你带回修道院
We want to bring you back to the convent.
好吧
All right.
好了 我们走
All right, let's go.
我还需要那个
I'm gonna need that back.
穿上袍子 钥匙
Put on the habit. Key. Oh, key!
好吧
Okay. All right.
我们走
Let's go. Let's go, let's go.
你觉得这和我们剪头发有关吗?
You think this has something to do with our hair being cut?
你觉得我们应该告诉布鲁诺吗?
You think we should tell Bruno about that?
他手里满是他妻子墙上的东西
He's got his hands full with the wife in the wall and everything.
我们刚刚看到了最疯狂的事情 你不会相信的
We just saw the wildest thing. You would not believe it.
那是一只海龟
Well, it was a turtle...
快
Come on.
你好
Hello.
妥玛索
Tommasso.
修道院的情况如何?
How are things at the convent?
很孤独
It's lonely.
那座修道院太无聊了
That monastery is so boring.
我们所做的就是祈祷
All we do is pray.
我的意思是 这很重要 但是
I mean, it's important, but...
都是因为男人
It's all men.
看到你的脸真好
It's so good to see your face.
有人来了
Someone's coming.
快
Come on!
Come on.
她们都走了
They're gone.
好了 走吧
All right, come on.
首杀字幕组 [疯狂修道院 V1版] 20170924